<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>life on The Rules</title>
    <link>https://antonvin.com/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in life on The Rules</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:02:47 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antonvin.com/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#21 - Consumerism</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/21-consumerism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 19:02:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/21-consumerism/</guid>
      <description>This very rule is reminiscent of Rule #19. You can miss your chance in a similar way. But before you start arguing, hear me out on this one.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve decided on an item you wish to purchase, you&amp;rsquo;ve done your homework, have compared it against numerous similar items, and truly have set your mind on this one, then&amp;hellip;
 Rule #21: &amp;ldquo;Never delay your purchase for tomorrow because the item you wanted to buy today had been already sold yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#20 - Meet</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/20-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 18:39:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/20-meet/</guid>
      <description>Every single person on our planet can teach us something new. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not a mercantile rule. Connections rule in our life.
 Rule #20: &amp;ldquo;Meet, don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid.&amp;rdquo;
 Every time you meet new people, it improves your mood, also introduces new opportunities to be a better self, and extends horizons in every possible direction.
 Originally created and published in Mar 2010</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#19 - Travel</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/19-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 18:11:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/19-travel/</guid>
      <description>We don&amp;rsquo;t get better over time. With every passing day, our abilities and capabilities to do something useful deplete. 1
Many people dream of traveling somewhere nice and beautiful. But in the future, we won&amp;rsquo;t have that much energy and resources to do so. We will all have our commitments to take care of or rather to serve to such as a mortgage, car loans, work, significant others. You know that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#16 - Empty Carriage</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/16-empty-carriage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 13:23:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/16-empty-carriage/</guid>
      <description>Here is an illustration for you to fuel up your associations. Life is akin to a railroad we are moving along towing the carriages as if we were a locomotive. The carriages represent the people, the items, and the objects we value and love in our life. We, the engine attached to the front of the train, shoulder all the weight and responsibilities. When we start feeling that some of the carriages are empty, it only adds up weight with no significant benefit to us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#6 - Grounding and Bonding</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/6-grounding-and-bonding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 21:36:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/6-grounding-and-bonding/</guid>
      <description>We are surrounded by items and people we like. Even more, some of them we genuinely love. However, unfortunately, an effect comes into place after we&amp;rsquo;ve spent a significant amount of time with the before-mentioned, akin to a static electricity accumulation.
The static electricity is made of fatigue and banality.
A similar thing happens to you at work. It&amp;rsquo;s barely possible to love the work over a long period. As a solution to that, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to leave for a vacation occasionally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#5 - Black and White</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/5-black-and-white/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 21:10:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/5-black-and-white/</guid>
      <description>Life doesn&amp;rsquo;t consist of black and white. There are always the shades of grey which fill the void between them with a gradient. In life, nothing can be unequivocally evaluated. I can only say with a degree of certainty that objectivity is vague and can be arguably existent in mathematics and physics. Also, people say there is some level of objectivity while looking through the viewfinder of a video recorder.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
