<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Rules</title>
    <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Rules</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 18:39:16 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antonvin.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#20 - Meet</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/20-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 18:39:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/20-meet/</guid>
      <description>Every single person on our planet can teach us something new. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not a mercantile rule. Connections rule in our life.
 Rule #20: &amp;ldquo;Meet, don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid.&amp;rdquo;
 Every time you meet new people, it improves your mood, also introduces new opportunities to be a better self, and extends horizons in every possible direction.
 Originally created and published in Mar 2010</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#19 - Travel</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/19-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 18:11:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/19-travel/</guid>
      <description>We don&amp;rsquo;t get better over time. With every passing day, our abilities and capabilities to do something useful deplete. 1
Many people dream of traveling somewhere nice and beautiful. But in the future, we won&amp;rsquo;t have that much energy and resources to do so. We will all have our commitments to take care of or rather to serve to such as a mortgage, car loans, work, significant others. You know that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#18 - Depreciation</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/18-depreciation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 17:36:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/18-depreciation/</guid>
      <description>Rule #18: &amp;ldquo;Never forget about depreciation.&amp;rdquo;
 You can refuse the usefulness of this rule but you can never refuse the existence of depreciation expense.
Oftentimes depreciation expense takes up a significant portion of a cost that is being used. Here is an example related to car ownership. It makes my hair move just looking at this graph. In other words, that is how depreciation deceitfully hides in cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#17 - Grammatically Correct</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/17-grammatically-correct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 14:17:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/17-grammatically-correct/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes when I am browsing the internet I get upset quite easily. In the comment sections, people express themselves incorrectly with spelling and grammar errors. It was a bigger deal back in my old country, Russia. However, the English domain suffers from that too.
You would argue, who am I, a non-native speaker, to critic and bash on how English people express their feelings in writing. Honestly, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter what language you speak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#16 - Empty Carriage</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/16-empty-carriage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 13:23:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/16-empty-carriage/</guid>
      <description>Here is an illustration for you to fuel up your associations. Life is akin to a railroad we are moving along towing the carriages as if we were a locomotive. The carriages represent the people, the items, and the objects we value and love in our life. We, the engine attached to the front of the train, shoulder all the weight and responsibilities. When we start feeling that some of the carriages are empty, it only adds up weight with no significant benefit to us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#15 - Preparation</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/15-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:42:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/15-preparation/</guid>
      <description> Rule #15: &amp;ldquo;Always go an extra mile in preparation for important events. Do a little more.&amp;rdquo; 1
 There is always a margin for error in preparations similar to those in mathematical calculations. An extra effort will allow you to minimize the error effects.
  Originally created and published in Mar 2010 &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#14 - Start Over Again</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/14-start-over-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:16:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/14-start-over-again/</guid>
      <description>Due to the nature of my work, I design-support the consulting engineers with equipment and system selections. Over time, working on a specific project we go through many revision iterations. I duplicate, say, &amp;lsquo;Revision 0&amp;rsquo; into &amp;lsquo;Revision 1&amp;rsquo; and modify the content to tailor it to the new conditions and requests. Then &amp;lsquo;Revision 2&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Revision 3&amp;rsquo; emerge. However, there is a moment in time when it&amp;rsquo;s hard to track all of the changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#13 - Foreign Languages</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/13-foreign-languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 23:22:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/13-foreign-languages/</guid>
      <description> Rule #12: &amp;ldquo;Learn foreign languages.&amp;rdquo; 1
 Learn at least one of the major ones such as French, German, Spanish. 2
  Originally created and published in Mar 2010 &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;
 It depends on your country of origin, of course. For instance, for Russian native speakers, the list would be English, French, German. &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#12 - Immediate Tasks</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/12-immediate-tasks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 17:52:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/12-immediate-tasks/</guid>
      <description>Who wrote military regulations? The very bluebook of &amp;ldquo;Regulations for the Order and Discipline of the Troops.&amp;rdquo; I am pretty sure there is an author or a group of authors to that. But I truly believe that life is the true author of military regulations. Salty sweat and sticky blood of the soldiers seal all the chapters of the book. Same with &amp;ldquo;The Rules&amp;rdquo;, — life is the true author of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#11 - Money and Happiness</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/11-money-and-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 16:21:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/11-money-and-happiness/</guid>
      <description>Gift a loaf of bread to a poor boy from the slums in a remote village. He&amp;rsquo;ll be in the seventh heaven of happiness and delight.
Gift a new car to a rich boy from a luxury mansion in a wealthy neighborhood. He&amp;rsquo;ll probably be in the seventh heaven of happiness and delight, either.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare the level of happiness for both of the boys; it&amp;rsquo;s roughly identical. However, the amount of money spent on the loaf of bread and the car is drastically different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#10 - Greed</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/10-greed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:20:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/10-greed/</guid>
      <description>Tell me, what is that? Some sort of greed to fill up your coffee mug full up to the rim? Like that:
And then, with a peculiar gait, trying not to spill it, carry it to a dining table. I just looked through my window and didn&amp;rsquo;t see a war, or a burst of hunger there, which would cause us to fight for every single ounce and milliliter of boiling water for our drinks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#9 - Perfect Love</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/9-perfect-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 22:54:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/9-perfect-love/</guid>
      <description>They kiss each other tenderly. Mouth to mouth. The movie credits start rolling up. What is going to happen next? For some reason that stays behind the scenes all the time. They have gone through fire and water to get to their goal. Love. But how is love continued? Here is the kiss he&amp;rsquo;s been fighting for throughout the entire movie.
True love is an attempt to grow something meaningful on the fertile soil of your broken heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#8 - Hand Brake</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/8-hand-brake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 19:50:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/8-hand-brake/</guid>
      <description>I bet you can relate to the following: you get into the car, start the engine, been driving for a while and suddenly you smell it. A distinct smell of something burning. The hand brake! You glimpse at the e-brake lever, and it&amp;rsquo;s engaged. &amp;ldquo;Oh dummy me,&amp;rdquo; you think.
Another one. In winter. Parked your car at night and as a matter of habit, you engage your e-brake. In the morning, when the brake pads froze to the rotors you can&amp;rsquo;t even move the car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#7 - A Simple Solution</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/7-a-simple-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 17:54:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/7-a-simple-solution/</guid>
      <description>Rule #7: &amp;ldquo;Every problem has a simple solution.&amp;rdquo; 1
 If it seems there is no simple solution to a problem, that means the solution is yet to be found. Only a shortsighted mind that is bound to overcomplicate things, is burdened to block itself in a dead-end of a thought process. Trust me, even seemingly unsolvable problems have a solution. Here is an example.
No human is perfect. I am colorblind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#6 - Grounding and Bonding</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/6-grounding-and-bonding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 21:36:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/6-grounding-and-bonding/</guid>
      <description>We are surrounded by items and people we like. Even more, some of them we genuinely love. However, unfortunately, an effect comes into place after we&amp;rsquo;ve spent a significant amount of time with the before-mentioned, akin to a static electricity accumulation.
The static electricity is made of fatigue and banality.
A similar thing happens to you at work. It&amp;rsquo;s barely possible to love the work over a long period. As a solution to that, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to leave for a vacation occasionally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#5 - Black and White</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/5-black-and-white/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 21:10:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/5-black-and-white/</guid>
      <description>Life doesn&amp;rsquo;t consist of black and white. There are always the shades of grey which fill the void between them with a gradient. In life, nothing can be unequivocally evaluated. I can only say with a degree of certainty that objectivity is vague and can be arguably existent in mathematics and physics. Also, people say there is some level of objectivity while looking through the viewfinder of a video recorder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#4 - Always Follow the Rules</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/4-follow-the-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 20:56:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/4-follow-the-rules/</guid>
      <description>Hey, I guess we are warming up here. Here is another small one.
 Rule #4: &amp;ldquo;Always Follow the Rules.&amp;rdquo; 1
 And, yes, I know, some of you would argue that there are occasions where you would step aside from following certain rules. I know it; everyone knows it. I won&amp;rsquo;t waste time talking about that.
Nonetheless, some of us follow the rules subconsciously.
All in all, if you want that everything goes smoothly, follow the rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#3 - Propulsion</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/3-propulsion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 22:55:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/3-propulsion/</guid>
      <description>Propulsion creates a driving force leading to movement. It makes the world go around, makes people achieve the goals and desired dreams. Everything in the world moves because of the nature of propulsion. Where it comes from, that hidden force?
For instance, wind derives its driving force from the pressure difference in two points. Electricity, from the electric potential difference. Sensible heat, from the temperature difference. What about people? What is a driving force for us, human beings?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#2 - One Dish Meal</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/2-one-dish-meal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 22:28:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/2-one-dish-meal/</guid>
      <description>I am pretty sure you have done this before: you’d ordered the main course, salad, and an appetizer in a restaurant and then realized you are not going to finish the entire dish. Your stomach simply couldn’t accommodate all that tasty food.
The same story happened with my friends and me in Munich (Germany, Bavaria). In a restaurant by the central railway station, we decided to make an order. I was hungry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1 - Did I Forget Something?</title>
      <link>https://antonvin.com/blog/1-did-i-forget-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 22:19:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antonvin.com/blog/1-did-i-forget-something/</guid>
      <description>If my memory serves me right, I wanted to tell you something. However, I have no recollection of what it was.
 Well, rule #1 then: “Never rely on your memory. Every major thing has to be written down.” 1, 2
   Originally created and published in Jan 2010 &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;
 👋 — Hello, 2020 Anton here, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to imagine a better rule during the pandemic time. An idea is not worth even a dime if it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been written down.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
